look at the [__] siren on that guy
holy
[__] that [__] [__] is not
coming
off [__] let me tell you something all
you'd have to do is be able to hook a
trailer to this and if you're a
carpenter you now live in your work
truck dude that's the battery bank right
there it's already set up you know if
any of the motors are locked up I have
no idea I had them all between five of
them I'm sure we can get at least two or
three good it's already wired up all I
have to do is get 30 amps at 240 right
there actually probably
120 another spare transmission this is
great that would be the transmission
already
out they're all Ford engine but those
two are decent do you know what the best
part about this is you can get something
from me and I can get something from you
and neither one of us is going to pay
elix taxes every time we change money
the government takes between 8 and 33%
do you want to track or anything you I
don't know me neither you know why I
like to building buses this [__] is
awesome man and I love tricking it out
but I really want you to go with me for
one day and one night out on the van
light trip you'll even get your own bed
dog don't worry that way you can see
what it's like to exist in one because
if you never spend any time in one you
really don't have any parameters we'll
take you in to the lake all right let's
go